http://www.ddfl.org/privacy-policy/

The Dumb Friends League has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our website. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for the website located at the URL support.ddfl.org.
In order to fully understand your rights, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms of Use. The Dumb Friends League reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of:
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the siteWho collects such informationHow such information is usedWith whom your information may be sharedWhat choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your informationWhat kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control, andHow you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Dumb Friends League by sending an email to info@ddfl.org. Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information
Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, format preference (HTML vs. text), address, interests and similar information. We do not request or store sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card or social security numbers.
Donor Information
For your privacy, the Dumb Friends League does not sell, rent, lend or exchange our mailing or contributor lists.
Personal information such as name, email and physical address collected online or offline is not shared or sold.
Internet Protocol Address
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our site, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Use of “Cookies”
Our site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our site. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for recordkeeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes Web surfing easier by performing certain functions, such as saving your passwords and your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website, and making sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.
Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them.
Security
All information provided to the Dumb Friends League is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of the Dumb Friends League. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
Tell-A-Friend
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. The Dumb Friends League will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. The Dumb Friends League stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
Other Websites
Our site contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which the Dumb Friends League has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites, as their policies may be different from ours.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, you can contact us by email or write us at Dumb Friends League, 2080 S. Quebec St., Denver, CO 80231.
Follow us
Become a Dumb Friends League insider
Sign up for emails
Contact us
Get in touch
